Guide to the John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0700
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 2008-2009; Accession ARCH-2011-074
  - Solicitations (4 of 4), 05/07/2009-08/31/2009; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Admissions (1 of 2), 04/14/2008-02/05/2009; AD 8.1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Admissions (2 of 2), 02/06/2009-08/31/2009; AD 8.1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Student Affairs, 09/04/2008-07/07/2009; AD 8.8 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Residential and Dining Enterprises, 01/25/2008-08/24/2009; AD 8.18.11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Registrar, 02/23/2007-06/30/2009; AD 8.21 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Human Resources, 12/04/2008-08/24/2009; AD 10 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Employment Inquiries, 09/19/2008-08/12/2009; AD 10.1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Media and Publications, Misc. (1 of 3), 09/16/2008-12/01/2008; AD 11.8 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Media and Publications, Misc. (2 of 3), 12/02/2008-02/21/2009; AD 11.8 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Media and Publications, Misc. (3 of 3), 02/25/2009-07/13/2009; AD 11.8 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Surveys and Questionnaires, 10/03/2007-04/14/2009; AD 11.8.10 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Management Company, 11/01/2006-03/19/2009; AD 12.3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Budget Group, 11/13/2008-06/01/2009; AD 12.5 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Office of Development, 06/30/2008-06/15/2009; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Land, BLDGS and Real Estate, 02/09/2009-07/20/2009; AD 12.14 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Art Galleries and Museums, Misc., 04/30/2007-08/20/2009; AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Misc., 10/03/2008-08/31/2009; AD 13.10.1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Relations, 09/27/2007-08/25/2009; AL 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 04/22/2008-08/31/2009; AL 1.3 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, Misc., 09/23/2003-02/26/2006; B 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Land and Building Campus Planning, BoT, 07/11/2003-04/03/2006; B 14.6 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Academic Secretary, 09/21/2004-07/16/2009; C 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Senate, Academic Council, 03/15/2005-04/20/2009; C 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Government/Community Rel., 09/30/2008-07/15/2009; G 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - California State Government, 10/30/2008-07/15/2009; G 1.2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Government, 10/03/2008-08/31/2009; G 3 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Education, U.S. Department of, 09/05/2007-07/22/2009; G 3.8.3 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Government Relations, 09/11/2008-08/24/2009; G 5 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 09/09/2008-04/27/2009; G 10 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital, 10/01/2007-05/27/2009; SHS 7 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 09/25/2008-07/21/2009; M 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Organizations (1 of 2), 09/04/2008-01/06/2009; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Organizations (2 of 2), 01/09/2009-08/25/2009; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - AAAS, 09/09/2008-06/23/2009; O 3.7 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - American Council on Education, 09/15/2008-08/24/2009; O 3.8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The National Academies, 09/12/2008-07/06/2009; O 3.43 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NCAA, 09/05/2008-08/19/2009; O 3.44 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pacific Ten Conference, 09/09/2008-07/01/2009; O 3.47 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Universities Research Association, 09/09/2008-08/10/2009; O 7.16 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Universities and Colleges, Misc., 12/03/2007-08/31/2009; O 8 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - AAU, 10/16/2008-08/31/2009; O 8.7 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Inaugurations, Misc., 09/06/2006-08/31/2009; O 8.55 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 09/05/2008-08/19/2009; ST 8 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- President's records, 2009-2010; Accession ARCH-2012-037
  - Faculty Development/Affairs, 01/01/2010-03/01/2010; AA 2.7 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Education, 03/04/2009-06/08/2010; AA 3 (Box 1)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 03/26/2010-07/07/2010; AA 3.5 (Box 1)
  - Continuing Studies, 03/30/2010-08/16/2010; AA 3.6 (Box 1)
  - Humanities and Sciences, School of, 10/07/2009-06/22/2010; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - SIEPR, 05/06/2008-08/16/2010; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1)
  - Athletics, Dept. of, 11/19/2008-7/27/2010; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution, 9/29/2009-5/10/2010; AA 4.9 (Box 1)
  - SULAIR, 10/08/2009-8/16/2010; AA 4.12 (Box 1)
  - Law, School of, 10/05/2009-8/02/2010; AA 4.15 (Box 1)
  - Awards and Prizes, Misc., 9/01/2009-8/31/2010; AA 5 (Box 1)
  - Grants and Scholarships, Miscellaneous, 9/10/2009-8/24/2010; AA 6 (Box 1)
  - Fellowships, Miscellaneous, 9/11/2009-8/24/2010; AA 8 (Box 1)
  - ROTC, 1/22/2010-7/14/2010; AD 2.26 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, General, 9/21/2009-8/16/2010; AD 4.20 (Box 1)
  - News articles, 10/12/2009-7/02/2010; AD 4.20.1 (Box 1)
  - Condolence Letters, 11/15/2007-8/09/2010; AD 4.20.2 (Box 1)
  - Appreciation Letters, 9/23/2009-8/02/2010; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 1)
  - Invitations (1 of 2), 9/01/2009-2/19/2010; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 1)
  - Invitations (2 of 2), 2/23/2010-8/31/2010; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 1)
  - Holiday Cards, 12/03/2009-4/01/2010; AD 4.20.4/4 (Box 1)
  - Nonsense, 9/02/2009-8/30/2010; AD 4.20.5 (Box 1)
  - Recommendation Letters, 9/16/2009-8/12/2010; AD 4.20.6 (Box 1)
  - Complaint Letters, 10/14/2008-7/08/2010; AD 4.20.7 (Box 2)
  - Solicitations (1 of 3), 10/16/2008-11/24/2009; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2)
  - Solicitations (2 of 3), 11/24/2009-3/12/2010; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2)
  - Solicitations (3 of 3), 3/12/2010-8/26/2010; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2)
  - Admissions, 9/04/2009-8/23/2010; AD 8.1 (Box 2)
  - Employment Inquiries, 8/25/2008-7/08/2010; AD 10.1 (Box 2)
  - Lively Arts, 10/03/2007-10/19/2009; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 2)
  - Media and Publications, Misc., 9/10/2009-8/23/2010; AD 11.8 (Box 2)
  - Conferences, Misc., 9/01/2009-8/24/2010; AD 13.10.1 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Relations, 9/01/2009-8/09/2010; AL 1 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 9/10/2009-8/24/2010; AL 1.3 (Box 2)
  - U.S. Government, 9/04/2009-8/26/2010; G 3 (Box 2)
  - National Science Foundation, 1/23/2008-6/28/2010; G 3.19 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Government Relations, 9/10/2009-8/10/2010; G 5 (Box 2)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 9/01/2009-7/27/2010; M 1 (Box 2)
  - Misc. Organizations, 9/10/2009-8/27/2010; O 1 (Box 3)
  - Educational Organizations, 8/12/2008-8/23/2010; O 3 (Box 3)
  - COFHE (1 of 2), 1/29/2008-1/12/2009; O 3.1 (Box 3)
  - COFHE (2 of 2), 3/16/2009-3/26/2010; O 3.1 (Box 3)
  - The National Academies, 10/08/2009-8/25/2010; O 3.43 (Box 3)
  - Universities and Colleges, Misc. (1 of 2), 3/17/2009-1/15/2010; O 8 (Box 3)
  - Universities and Colleges, Misc. (2 of 2), 1/21/2010-8/26/2010; O 8 (Box 3)
  - Student Groups, Misc., 10/09/2008-8/02/2010; ST 1.1 (Box 3)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 7/14/2009-8/02/2010; ST 8 (Box 3)
- President's records, 2010-2011; Accession ARCH-2013-076
  - Graduate Education, 12/15/2009-12/16/2010; AA 1.13 (Box 1)
  - Emeriti, 12/16/2010-6/2/2011; AA 2.2 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation Issues, 3/16/2010-4/21/2011; AA 3.4 (Box 1)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 9/24/2010-5/24/2011; AA 3.5 (Box 1)
  - Freshman/Sophomore College, 3/15/2010-3/17/2010; AA 3.18.2 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Sciences, 9/9/2010-5/6/2011; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - Humanities Center, 11/16/2009-5/19/2011; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1)
  - Department of Athletics, 9/4/2007-8/15/2011; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1)
  - Football Games, 8/23/2010-8/17/2011; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 1)
  - Graduate School of Business (GSB), 11/10/2009-5/19/2011; AA 4.2 (Box 1)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 11/15/2007-8/3/2010; AA 4.3 (Box 1)
  - Global Climate and Energy Project (GCEP), 10/9/2007-6/21/2011; AA 4.3.1 (Box 1)
  - School of Engineering, 9/3/2008-8/1/2011; AA 4.4 (Box 1)
  - School of Education, 9/25/2009-8/30/2011; AA 4.5 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution, 11/4/2010-8/23/2011; AA 4.9 (Box 1)
  - SULAIR, 9/17/2010-4/28/2011; AA 4.12 (Box 1)
  - Information Technology Services, 6/16/2009-8/17/2011; AA 4.22 (Box 1)
  - Awards & Prizes, 6/2/2010-8/31/2011; AA 5 (Box 1)
  - Grants & Scholarships, 9/10/2010-8/16/2011; AA 6 (Box 1)
  - Fellowships, 10/12/2010-5/3/2011; AA 8 (Box 1)
  - Fulbright Fellowship/Scholarships, 11/4/2009-3/15/2011; AA 8.16 (Box 1)
  - Tanner Lectures, 4/22/2009-7/6/2011; AA 9.19 (Box 1)
  - ROTC, 9/30/2010-6/20/2011; AD 2.26 (Box 1)
  - President's Office, 11/2/2007-8/12/2009; AD 4 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, General, 5/5/2000-8/3/2011; AD 4.20 (Box 1)
  - News Clippings/Editorials, 9/28/2010-8/23/2011; AD 4.20.1 (Box 1)
  - Condolence Letters, 6/2/2010-4/1/2011; AD 4.20.2 (Box 1)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 11/4/2009-7/25/2011; AD 4.20.3 (Box 1)
  - Appreciation letters, 6/1/2010-8/8/2011; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 1)
  - Invitations, 6/2/2009-8/30/2011; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 1)
  - Holiday, miscellaneous cards, 11/9/2010-3/18/2011; AD 4.20.4/4 (Box 1)
  - Nonsense, 9/9/2010-8/17/2011; AD 4.20.5 (Box 1)
  - Solicitations, 11/7/2003-8/31/2011; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2)
  - University Communications, 12/10/2009-7/13/2011; AD 4.22 (Box 2)
  - Admissions, 8/26/2010-8/23/2011; AD 8.1 (Box 2)
  - Office of Student Affairs, 12/15/2009-4/7/2011; AD 8.8 (Box 2)
  - Financial Aid, 3/10/2009-1/5/2011; AD 8.12 (Box 2)
  - Residential & Dining Enterprises, 5/28/2008-7/11/2011; AD 8.18.11 (Box 2)
  - Employment Inquiries, 12/12/2010-5/17/2011; AD 10.1 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Labor Action Coalition, Coalition for Labor Justice, 10/17/2008-5/18/2011; AD 10-SLAC/CLJ (Box 2)
  - Freshman issues, 9/28/2007-6/3/2009; AD 11.7.7 (Box 2)
  - Media & Publications, 9/25/2009-8/31/2011; AD 11.8 (Box 2)
  - Stanford University Press, 5/10/2006-7/11/2007; AD 11.8.9 (Box 2)
  - Media & Publications (Stanford internal), 7/5/2000-4/12/2011; AD 11.8.11 (Box 2)
  - Office of Development, 2/22/2010-5/17/2011; AD 12.10.1 (Box 2)
  - The Stanford Fund, 9/28/2006-5/13/2011; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 2)
  - Donor Relations, 10/11/2006-6/20/2011; AD 12.10.2/7 (Box 2)
  - The Stanford Challenge, 4/25/2008-6/14/2011; AD 12.10.2/8 (Box 2)
  - Asian Relations, 8/23/2000-1/31/2011; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 2)
  - Land, Buildings & Real Estate, 12/16/2009-8/3/2011; AD 12.14 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 9/21/2009-8/17/2011; AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 2)
  - Memorial Church, 9/22/2006-7/14/2011; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 2)
  - Parking & Transportation, 9/16/2008-3/10/2011; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 2)
  - Conferences, Miscellaneous, 10/26/2010-8/4/2011; AD 13.10.1 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 10/28/2003-8/10/2011; AL 1.3 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Events, Homecoming, Reunion, 10/9/2008-10/20/2010; AL 1.7 (Box 3)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 11/3/2005-8/15/2011; AL 3 & AL 3.1 (Box 3)
  - Board of Trustees Appointments & Resignations, 5/24/2005-1/5/2010; B 12 (Box 3)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 5/14/2004-5/11/2011; B 14 (Box 3)
  - Academic Secretary, 6/18/2009-7/25/2011; C 1 (Box 3)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 3/12/2010-5/19/2011; C 2 (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board of the Academic Council, 10/1/2004-8/19/2008; C 3 (Box 3)
  - Steering Committee of the Academic Council, 9/27/2004-6/18/2010; C 4.1 (Box 3)
  - Office of Government and Community Relations, 10/1/2009-7/19/2011; G 1 (Box 3)
  - California State Government, 3/4/2001-8/23/2011; G 1.2 (Box 3)
  - United States Government, 10/30/2007-8/15/2011; G 3 (Box 3)
  - Defense, Department of, 1/24/2008-1/25/2011; G 3.7 (Box 3)
  - Energy, Department of, 11/20/2007-8/25/2010; G 3.7.2 (Box 3)
  - NASA, 10/4/2006-1/7/2010; G 3.7.4 (Box 3)
  - Education, Department of, 10/15/2009-7/18/2011; G 3.8.3 (Box 3)
  - National Science Foundation, 9/14/2010-8/3/2011; G 3.19 (Box 3)
  - Local Government, 9/11/2006-8/15/2011; G 4 (Box 3)
  - Foreign Government Relations, 10/14/2009-8/22/2011; G 5 (Box 3)
  - California Institute for Federal Policy Research (CIFPR), 9/16/2008-10/3/2008; G 7 (Box 3)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 5/17/2006-4/26/2010; G 10 (Box 3)
  - United Nations, UNESCO, 10/10/2006-5/10/2010; G 12 (Box 3)
  - Auxiliary, Hospital, 9/1/1998-11/10/2003; SHS 1 (Box 3)
  - Stanford Hospital & Clinics Administration, 2/22/2008-7/26/2011; SHS 3 (Box 3)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute (HHMI), 11/17/2006-10/1/2010; SHS 9 (Box 3)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 4/27/2010-8/23/2011; M 1 (Box 3)
  - Institute for Stem Cell Biology and Regenerative Medicine, 11/22/2004-8/25/2008; M 5.1 (Box 3)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous, 11/8/2006-8/24/2011; O 1 (Box 3)
  - Council on Competitiveness (COC), 8/29/2007-4/1/2009; O 1.2 (Box 4)
  - Education Groups/Organizations, 5/14/2007-6/17/2011; O 3 (Box 4)
  - Consortium of Social Science Associations (COSSA), 9/21/2006-9/14/2009; O 3.3 (Box 4)
  - Association of Pacific Rim Universities (APRU), APEC, 9/12/2008-11/22/2010; O 3.4 (Box 4)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences (AAAS), 11/4/2009-8/30/2011; O 3.7 (Box 4)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 4/2/2010-6/21/2011; O 3.8 (Box 4)
  - National Association of Independendent Colleges and Universities (NAICU), 9/22/2008-6/10/2011; O 3.10 (Box 4)
  - The College Board, 10/30/2008-8/15/2011; O 3.25 (Box 4)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), 10/26/2006-9/16/2009; O 3.38 (Box 4)
  - The National Academies, 7/21/2000-8/10/2011; O 3.43 (Box 4)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 9/10/2009-8/17/2011; O 3.44 (Box 4)
  - Pacific-10 Conference (PAC-10), 9/10/2009-6/20/2011; O 3.47 (Box 4)
  - Athletic Organizations, 1/6/2009-10/2/2010; O 4 (Box 4)
  - Universities & Colleges, Miscellaneous, 8/29/2000-8/17/2011; O 8 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU), 7/24/2000-7/25/2011; O 8.7 (Box 4)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges (AGB), 6/8/2006-10/21/2009; O 8.8 (Box 4)
  - Association of Independent CA Colleges and Universities (AICCU), 11/28/2006-10/9/2008; O 8.9 (Box 4)
  - Harvard University, 9/21/2006-11/10/2010; O 8.23 (Box 5)
  - Princeton University, 3/30/2007-1/14/2011; O 8.36 (Box 5)
  - University of California, 12/1/2006-7/18/2011; O 8.43 (Box 5)
  - University of Michigan, 10/24/2005-2/20/2008; O 8.45 (Box 5)
  - University of Oregon, 5/30/2006-7/15/2008; O 8.47 (Box 5)
  - University of Southern California (USC), 3/7/2007-7/18/2011; O 8.49 (Box 5)
  - Western Association of Schools & Colleges (WASC), 6/7/2005-3/9/2011; O 8.52 (Box 5)
  - Yale University, 11/28/2005-6/13/2011; O 8.53 (Box 5)
  - Inaugurations (Other Schools), 9/10/2009-8/30/2011; O 8.55 (Box 5)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum (BAEF), Bay Area Council, Baytrade, 10/10/2008-8/15/2011; O 11 (Box 5)
  - California Council on Science and Technology (CCST), 9/16/2004-1/4/2011; O 12 (Box 5)
  - American Philosophical Society (APS), 6/5/2006-5/23/2011; O 15 (Box 5)
  - Vice Provost and Dean of Research, 10/31/2006-1/3/2011; R 0 (Box 5)
  - Freeman Spogli Institute for International Studies (FSI), 12/8/2006-6/10/2011; R 1.12 (Box 5)
  - The Initiative on the Environment and Sustainability, 2/13/2007-3/1/2010; R 4.2 (Box 5)
  - Woods Institute for the Environment, 10/11/2007-7/8/2009; R 4.2.1 (Box 5)
  - The International Initiative, 3/30/2007-8/28/2007; R 4.3 (Box 5)
  - Student Groups, 1/12/2011-8/17/2011; ST 1.1 (Box 5)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU), 1/12/2009-8/24/2011; ST 2 (Box 5)
  - KZSU Student Radio, 10/4/2005-8/28/2007; ST 3.18 (Box 5)
  - Haas Center for Public Service, 4/25/2007-12/10/2010; ST 3.29 (Box 5)
  - Campus Compact, 9/14/2006-6/21/2011; ST 3.35 (Box 5)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 9/7/2010-7/28/2011; ST 8 (Box 5)
- President's records, 2013; Accession ARCH-2014-068
  - Signed photographs of New York City Michael Bloomberg at Bing Concert Hall, 2013 Jun 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- President's records, 2011-2012; Accession ARCH-2014-113
  - Undergraduate Education, 9/25/2008-2/2/2012; AA 3 (Box 1)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 4/4/2012-7/3/2012; AA 3.5 (Box 1)
  - Summer Programs, Summer Session, 9/11/2009-6/27/2012; AA 3.16 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Sciences, 3/29/2012-5/31/2012; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - Department of Art, 8/7/2008-12/1/2011; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1)
  - Department of Athletics, 9/12/2011-8/21/2012; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1)
  - Football Games, Rose Bowl, 9/12/2011-2/2/2012; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution, 9/7/2011-8/13/2012; AA 4.9 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Libraries, 12/5/2011-8/28/2012; AA 4.12 (Box 1)
  - CSLI/ EPGY, 3/21/2006-5/7/2012; AA 4.14.1 (Box 1)
  - Law School, 9/21/2010-1/31/2012; AA 4.15 (Box 1)
  - Awards & Prizes, 9/20/2011-8/28/2012; AA 5 (Box 1)
  - Grants & Scholarships, 9/7/2011-8/28/2012; AA 6 (Box 1)
  - Fellowships, 9/28/2011-1/18/2012; AA 8 (Box 1)
  - Knight Fellowships/Knight Foundation, 7/1/2010-5/25/2011; AA 8.25 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Miscellaneous, 4/10/2000-9/4/2007; AD 1 (Box 1)
  - News Clippings/Editorials, 9/14/2011-5/7/2012; AD 4.20.1 (Box 1)
  - Condolence Letters, 9/15/2011-6/13/2012; AD 4.20.2 (Box 1)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 5/18/2005-8/15/2012; AD 4.20.3 (Box 1)
  - Appreciation letters, 9/21/2011-8/28/2012; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 1)
  - Invitations, 9/13/2011-8/31/2012; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 1)
  - Holiday/Miscelleanous Cards, 12/5/2011-8/21/2012; AD 4.20.4/4 (Box 1)
  - Nonsense, 8/29/2011-8/31/2012; AD 4.20.5 (Box 1)
  - Nominations, 9/21/2010-2/2/2012; AD 4.20.6 (Box 1)
  - Solicitations, 8/23/2011-8/31/2012; AD 4.20.8 (Box 1)
  - Solicitations, 8/23/2011-8/31/2012; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2)
  - University Communications, 10/31/2011-8/28/2012; AD 4.22 (Box 2)
  - Admissions, 12/14/2010-8/31/2012; AD 8.1 (Box 2)
  - Office of Student Affairs, 1/12/2010-7/30/2012; AD 8.8 (Box 2)
  - Vaden Health Center, 5/22/2009-3/3/2011; AD 8.9 (Box 2)
  - Bing Overseas Studies, 12/16/2008-4/1/2011; AD 8.11 (Box 2)
  - Financial Aid, 9/29/2008-12/3/2008; AD 8.12 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Housing, 9/16/2008-8/12/2010; AD 8.18 (Box 2)
  - Residential & Dining Enterprises, 9/28/2009-11/7/2011; AD 8.18.11 (Box 2)
  - Residential Education, 1/29/2007-3/12/2012; AD 8.18.13 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources, 10/27/2009-4/5/2011; AD 10 (Box 2)
  - Employment Inquiries, 9/7/2011-8/28/2012; AD 10.1 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Events, 10/8/2007-3/19/2009; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 2)
  - Lively Arts, 5/10/2011-4/30/2012; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 2)
  - Media & Publications, 9/19/2011-8/2/2012; AD 11.8 (Box 2)
  - Surveys, Questionnaires, 2/4/2011-2/14/2012; AD 11.8.10 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Management Company, 5/18/2010-5/31/2012; AD 12.3 (Box 2)
  - Budget Group, 12/3/2008-8/20/2012; AD 12.5 (Box 2)
  - Office of Development, 10/19/2011-8/15/2012; AD 12.10.1 (Box 2)
  - Asian Relations, 10/5/2011-5/16/2012; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 2)
  - Land, Buildings, & Real Estate, 9/6/2011-8/3/2012; AD 12.14 (Box 2)
  - Conferences, Miscellaneous, 10/7/2011-7/11/2012; AD 13.10.1 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Relations, 10/5/2005-2/14/2012; AL 1 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 11/3/2010-8/8/2012; AL 1.3 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Board of Trustees, 9/30/2010-8/13/2012; B 1 (Box 2)
  - Academic Secretary, 12/13/2011-8/28/2012; C 1 (Box 2)
  - Office of Government and Community Relations, 10/14/2011-7/3/2012; G 1 (Box 2)
  - California State Government, 9/1/2011-8/3/2012; G 1.2 (Box 2)
  - United States Government Relations, 3/3/2011-8/27/2012; G 3 (Box 2)
  - U.S. Department of Health & Human Services, 1/16/2007-4/7/2011; G 3.8.1 (Box 2)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 10/13/2011-7/23/2012; G 3.8.3 (Box 3)
  - National Science Foundation, 9/7/2011-8/13/2012; G 3.19 (Box 3)
  - Local Government, 9/1/2011-8/17/2012; G 4 (Box 3)
  - Foreign Government, 10/31/2011-8/20/2012; G 5 (Box 3)
  - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital, 12/6/2010-5/7/2012; SHS 7 (Box 3)
  - Affiliated Hospitals, Centers & Clinics, 10/19/2006-9/7/2011; SHS 13 (Box 3)
  - School of Medicine, 11/16/2011-7/12/2012; M 1 (Box 3)
  - School of Medicine Departments, Miscellaneous, 9/28/2006-6/22/2012; M 5 (Box 3)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous, 9/6/2011-8/20/2012; O 1 (Box 3)
  - Education Groups/Organizations, 12/5/2011-8/31/2012; O 3 (Box 3)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, 9/29/2011-6/13/2012; O 3.7 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education, 2/28/2012-7/20/2012; O 3.8 (Box 3)
  - NAICU, 7/26/2000-8/15/2012; O 3.10 (Box 3)
  - The National Academies, 12/5/2011-8/31/2012; O 3.43 (Box 3)
  - NCAA, 9/1/2011-8/28/2012; O 3.44 (Box 3)
  - Pacific-12 Conference, 9/7/2011-6/1/2012; O 3.47 (Box 3)
  - Athletic Organizations, 1/12/2012-8/17/2012; O 4 (Box 3)
  - Universities Research Association, 12/7/2009-3/13/2012; O 7.16 (Box 3)
  - Universities & Colleges, 6/11/2009-8/15/2012; O 8 (Box 3)
  - Association of American Universities, 12/1/2011-4/25/2012; O 8.7 (Box 3)
  - California State Universities, 9/7/2007-8/7/2012; O 8.17 (Box 3)
  - Peking University, 3/26/2006-6/26/2012; O 8.30 (Box 3)
  - University of California, 10/11/2011-7/3/2012; O 8.43 (Box 3)
  - University of Chicago, 10/11/2005-7/31/2006; O 8.44 (Box 3)
  - University of Southern California, 11/12/2009-8/31/2012; O 8.49 (Box 3)
  - Inaugurations, 8/23/2011-8/22/2012; O 8.55 (Box 3)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 11/14/2011-8/13/2012; O 11 (Box 3)
  - American Philosophical Society, 12/15/2011-7/31/2012; O 15 (Box 3)
  - Vice Provost and Dean of Research, 10/21/2011-8/28/2012; R 0 (Box 3)
  - Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, 7/20/2000-9/19/2008; R 1.8 (Box 3)
  - Students, Miscellaneous, 3/11/2009-6/26/2012; ST 1 (Box 3)
  - KZSU Student Radio, 1/20/2006-3/6/2012; ST 3.18 (Box 3)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 11/9/2010-7/3/2012; ST 8 (Box 3)
- Photographs, 2011-04-07; Accession ARCH-2015-086
  - Barack Obama letter and photograph to John Hennessy, 2011-04-07 (Box 1)
- President's records, 2000-2013; Accession ARCH-2015-138
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted 20 years from end of tenure.
  - Provost’s Office, 10/14/2011 - 1/15/2013; AA 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Education, 3/23/2012 - 4/4/2013; AA 1_13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Emeriti, 9/15/2011 - 12/9/2013; AA 2_2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Development, 11/15/2006 - 10/8/2012; AA 2_7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Education, 9/18/2012 - 8/7/2013; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Accreditation Issues, 4/12/2012 - 8/22/2013; AA 3_4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 4/15/2013 - 5/3/2013; AA 3_5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - School of Humanities Sciences, 3/28/2011 - 7/15/2013; AA 4_1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Computer Science, Dept. of, 8/13/2012 - 10/26/2012; AA 4_1_17 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - SIEPR, 4/14/2012 - 8/13/2013; AA 4_1_20_1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - English, Dept. of, 2/9/2009 - 9/10/2009; AA 4_1_21 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - History, Department of, 2/17/2010 - 4/3/2013; AA 4_1_25 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 12/3/2009 - 1/7/2013; AA 4_1_28 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Music, Dept. of, 12/17/2010 - 3/19/2013; AA 4_1_29 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Department of Athletics, 10/3/2012 - 7/16/2013; AA 4_1_30 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Football Games, Rose Bowl, 9/11/2012 - 8/27/2013; AA 4_1_30_1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Physics, Department of, 12/31/2009 - 7/3/2013; AA 4_1_33 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Political Science, Dept. of, 4/5/2007 - 10/22/2009; AA 4_1_34 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 11/20/2008 - 5/11/2011; AA 4_1_35 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - GSB, 6/1/2009 - 7/11/2013; AA 4_2 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Engineering, School of, 3/27/2012 - 8/21/2013; AA 4_4 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Education, School of, 11/21/2011 - 6/3/2013; AA 4_5 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Hoover Institution, 10/9/2012 - 8/26/2013; AA 4_9 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - SCIL, 6/20/2011 - 6/30/2011; AA 4_10_4 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CISAC, 6/29/2012 - 2/19/2013; AA 4_10_6 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Stanford University Libraries, 9/4/2012 - 8/6/2013; AA 4_12 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - CSLI/ EPGY, 2/6/2007 - 3/28/2013; AA 4_14_1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Law School, 9/5/2012 - 7/29/2013; AA 4_15 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - IT Services Admin. Systems, 9/20/2012 - 8/14/2013; AA 4_22 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Awards Prizes (1 of 2), 9/10/2012 - 2/6/2013; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Awards Prizes (2 of 2), 2/6/2013 - 8/22/2013; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Gold Spike Award, 3/16/2007 - 12/5/2011; AA 5_26 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Grants Scholarships, 9/4/2012 - 8/6/2013; AA 6 (Box 1, Folder 33)